What do you feel like was the point where you started to figure out, okay, they listening now?
Like, what was that point like?
How did that feel?
It was when we truly learned to connect instead of educate.
What you see in the film, The Feminist on Cell Block, Why, was shot after we had been running the program for four years.
So we had learned a lot.
The very first patriarchy workshop we did, we were like, we were all in small groups.
We would read these excerpts from Bell Hook's books.
And it didn't really work because not even the facilitators were on board.
And it just was giving schools.
Yeah, it took years to even organize the facilitators.
Nobody was feeling me, Amanda.
Nobody.
Thank God I had a community, like I said, of women and non-binary people on the outside.
So I didn't feel like a complete f***ing weirdo on the inside.
Why did they think it was so f***ing weird?
For the same reason white people don't want to talk about racism.
Because it's uncomfortable and it's where they've learned to build their needs and their confidence in as a human being.